<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sway</string>
    <string name="measurement_service_handler_name">cmsc436.umd.edu.measurement_service_handler</string>
    <string name="test_instr">Hello, and again, welcome to the Aperture Science Enrichment Center.
        We are currently experiencing technical difficulties due to circumstances of potentially
        apocalyptic significance beyond our control. However, thanks to Emergency Testing Protocols,
        testing can continue. These pre-recorded messages will provide instructional and
        motivational support, so that science can still be done, even in the event of environmental,
        social, economic, or structural collapse. . . For the first exam please stand with your legs spread.
        . . . stand still. . . The portal will open and emergency testing will begin in three. Two. One.
    </string>

    <string name="test_instr_1">
       Hello, This is the First Test of the Balance Tests. In this test I will need you to spread you legs to your shoulder width,. \n to start the test double tap with two fingers on the screen, or say go
    </string>

    <string name="test_instr_2">
        Hello, this is the second of the Balance Tests. In this test I will need you keep your legs closed, so that they are touching each other, and keep your eyes open
        ,. \n to start the test double tap with two fingers on the screen, or say go
    </string>

    <string name="test_instr_3">
        Hello, this is the third of the Balance Tests. In this test I will need you keep your legs closed, so that they are touching each other, keep your eyes closed
        ,. \n to start the test double tap with two fingers on the screen, or say go
    </string>

    <string name="test_instr_practice">
        Hello, this is the practice Balance Tests. Please Stand However you would like.\n double tap with two fingers on the screen to start the test
    </string>

    <string name="countdown">Now We can start the test in five. . . . four. . . . three. . . . two. . . . one</string>


    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <!--Help mode should display instructions or a guide to using the specific test, and then switch to Practice mode.-->
    <string name="instruction_overview">
        Welcome to the user instruction guide for the Sway Test.
        The Sway Test will consist of three different tests.
        Swipe left to view the instructions for each (specific) test.
        After viewing the instructions, the app will switch to Practice mode.
        Practice mode will allow you to practice the Sway Test as long as you want before exiting.
    </string>
    <string name="instruction_title">Instructions</string>

    <string name="ins_intro">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t \n\t Please swipe through the instructions for \teach test</string>
    <string name="text_1">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t \n\t TEST 1\n\t Please have legs opened and aligned with your shoulders</string>
    <string name="test_instr_text_2">\t\t\t\t\tTEST 2 \n\n Please have your legs closed \nand eyes opened</string>
    <string name="test_instr_text_3">\t\t\t\t\tTEST 3 \n\n Please have your legs closed and eyes closed</string>

    <string name="ins_1">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t \n\t TEST 1\n\t Please have legs opened and aligned with your shoulders</string>
    <string name="ins_2">\t\t\t\t\tTEST 2 \n\n Please have your legs closed \nand eyes opened</string>
    <string name="ins_3">\t\t\t\t\tTEST 3 \n\n Please have your legs closed and eyes closed</string>

    <string name="text_with_paras">Instructions: You need to have eyes closed and\n legs opened</string>

    <string-array name="test_instr_text_1">
        <item>Test 1</item>
        <item>Please stand with your legs opened and aligned with your shoulders. Keep your eyes opened. </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="test_instr_text_2">
        <item>Test 2</item>
        <item>Please stand with your legs closed and your eyes opened.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="test_instr_text_3">
        <item>Test 3</item>
        <item>Please stand with your legs closed and your eyes closed.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="practice_text">
        <item>Practice</item>
        <item>Click the \"Start\" button to start <b>Practice Mode</b>.
            Practice mode will allow you to practice the Sway Test
            as long as you wish to before exiting.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
